<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>
Properties associated with the Cell Mechanism which allow it to be loaded into neuroConstruct.

Note the following: 
   The Cell Mechanism name should not contain spaces and should match the name of the directory it's in
   The name and description here will be replaced by the corresponding values in a ChannelML file if found
   The filenames for the mappings are relative to the cellMechanism/(cellMechInstanceName) directory
   Mechanism Type should only have values: Channel mechanism, Synaptic mechanism, Ion concentration, Point process, Gap junction

</comment>
<entry key="Description">Channel translated from the original .mod file used in Kole MH, Ilschner SU, Kampa BM, Williams SR, Ruben PC, Stuart GJ, Action potential generation requires a high sodium channel density in the axon initial segment. Nat Neurosci. 2008 Feb;11(2):178-86. 
        Kinetics were fit to data from Huguenard et al. (1988) and Hamill et al. (1991). Notes taken from orig mod file:
        
        qi is not well constrained by the data, since there are no points between -80 and -55.  So this was fixed at 5 while the thi1,thi2,Rg,Rd were optimized using a simplex least square proc

        voltage dependencies are shifted approximately from the best fit to give higher threshold

        May 2006, set thinf = -59 mV, tha  = -35 and vshift = 0 to account for AIS Na channel kinetics Kole, ANU, 2006</entry>
<entry key="NEURON mapping">ChannelML_v1.8.1_NEURONmod.xsl</entry>
<entry key="PSICS file requires compilation">false</entry>
<entry key="GENESIS mapping">ChannelML_v1.8.1_GENESIStab.xsl</entry>
<entry key="Implementation method">ChannelML based Cell Mechanism</entry>
<entry key="NEURON file requires compilation">true</entry>
<entry key="Mechanism Type">Channel mechanism</entry>
<entry key="PSICS mapping">ChannelML_v1.8.1_PSICS.xsl</entry>
<entry key="ChannelML file">NaChannel_newFormat.xml</entry>
<entry key="GENESIS file requires compilation">true</entry>
<entry key="Mechanism Name">nax_CML</entry>
<entry key="Mechanism Model">ChannelML based process</entry>
</properties>
